<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<CutSceneText>
	<Text label="URI00">You&apos;ve come, [%username]. I&apos;ve got another job for you.</Text>
	<Text label="KALLA01">This mission is strictly confidential.</Text>
	<Text label="URI02">We have received information of a murder plot amongst the Elyos. Its hard to believe, but apparently the perpetrator is a knight.</Text>
	<Text label="URI03">I&apos;m sure you know the influential Intelligence Staff Officer Keidian.</Text>
	<Text label="KALLA04">Has he been acting suspiciously of late?</Text>
	<Text label="SOL05">Now that you mention it... He seemed shocked by one of the messages he received.</Text>
	<Text label="URI06">I did think he probably hadn&apos;t just disappeared by chance. But we managed to find his hideout.</Text>
	<Text label="KALLA07">We think he is holed up somewhere in part of the ruined Barat House in the geothermal Barat Zone.</Text>
	<Text label="URI08">As you would expect from an Intelligence Staff Officer, he is a proficient writer. If he notices that we are after him, he will vanish into thin air.</Text>
	<Text label="URI09">But if you approach him without troops and claim to be a turncoat like him, you might gain his trust.</Text>
	<Text label="SOL10">Are you saying I have to take care of this guy by myself?</Text>
	<Text label="URI11">That would be good, but it&apos;s best to keep him alive at first so we can check a few things out.</Text>
	<Text label="KALLA12">There is a huge cellar in the Barat House. Use it.</Text>
	<Text label="URI13">This mission is strictly confidential as we don&apos;t know who is friend or foe.</Text>
	<Text label="KALLA14">We have drafted a fake letter containing information from the rebels. Show Keidian this letter.</Text>
	<Text label="URI15">If he turns up at the location mentioned in the letter, he&apos;ll give himself away.</Text>
	<Text label="SOL16">This symbol?</Text>
	<Text label="URI17">Exactly. It seems that the Templars of the Tower of Light are showing solidarity with him. So you must be careful.</Text>
	<Text label="KALLA18">We&apos;ll infiltrate the area with a few soldiers then wait for you. I&apos;m counting on you.</Text>
</CutSceneText>
