<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<CutSceneText>
	<Text label="Vellus00">Come closer, hero of the Tijerid realm!</Text>
	<Text label="Reahl01">I can&apos;t bring myself to imagine what might have become of Tijerid if you hadn&apos;t been here.</Text>
	<Text label="Reahl02">Please forgive me for not listening carefully to what you said.</Text>
	<Text label="Vellus03">It&apos;s crazy that the beastly Orcs came up with the idea of pretending to launch a frontal attack but then actually feeding poison into the town through the underwater canals.</Text>
	<Text label="Reahl04">There&apos;s no way an Orc could have devised such a clever idea.</Text>
	<Text label="Vellus05">It can&apos;t have been the Orcs! I&apos;m sure it was Yurid! As if his betrayal wasn&apos;t bad enough, he was hell-bent on wiping out an entire civilian population!</Text>
	<Text label="Reahl06">...</Text>
	<Text label="SOL07">We may have defeated Orc Captain Shandu on the canal, but we did not actually see him there.</Text>
	<Text label="Vellus08">We need to dispatch all men to look for him at once!</Text>
	<Text label="ALL09">We can&apos;t send out all our men for one turncoat. Anyway, all the men are exhausted after the battle with the Orcs.</Text>
	<Text label="Vellus10">Reol!</Text>
	<Text label="Vellus11">I spent a lot of time with Reol.</Text>
	<Text label="Vellus12">I tried to steer both of them onto the right path, but I think Yurid went astray because of my instructions.</Text>
	<Text label="Vellus13">I accept full responsibility for him. I will find Yurid and take him to task.</Text>
	<Text label="Reahl14">Bellus, calm down.</Text>
	<Text label="Reahl15">Yurid is my only brother. My brother was supposed to become a Daeva...</Text>
	<Text label="Reahl16">If my brother had become a Daeva, the situation would never have escalated like this.</Text>
	<Text label="Reahl17">Just leave this to me.</Text>
	<Text label="Vellus18">Yes. As you wish.</Text>
	<Text label="Reahl19">Oh, I&apos;m sorry. I&apos;d completely forgotten the heroic [%username], the saviour of Tijerid.</Text>
	<Text label="Reahl20">I would like to express my gratitude to you on behalf of Tijerid.</Text>
	<Text label="SOL21">It was nothing, really.</Text>
	<Text label="Reahl22">Your gift will be waiting for you with Knight Telia outside the Audience Chamber.</Text>
	<Text label="Reahl23">It may not seem like much compared to your great deeds, but I beg you to be prepared to help us again.</Text>
</CutSceneText>
