<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<CutSceneText>
	<Text label="REAL01">Ah, here comes [%username]. I called you here because I have a very special mission for you.</Text>
	<Text label="REAL02">Have you heard that the Orcs&apos; attacks are becoming increasingly violent? That&apos;s what the mission is about.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS03">Of course, the attacks by these useless Orcs do not pose a serious threat to out Tijerid Army.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS04">But it is highly suspicious that they have been attacking weak points in the Tijerid Army of late.</Text>
	<Text label="REAL05">Incredibly, there are rumours that they know the exact weak points of the Occupation Troop.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS06">They are attacking only the key army facilities like supply and weapon stores.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS07">And when we notice this and launch a counterattack they disappear. It&apos;s almost as if they knew which route we are taking.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS08">Those troops haven&apos;t once been able to engage in combat with the Orcs.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS09">This has to mean that somebody with in-depth knowledge of our army is connected to the Orcs.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS10">And that same somebody must know all about clandestine troop movements.</Text>
	<Text label="REAL11">You can speak plainly.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS12">It is highly likely that one of the turncoats who attempted to murder the Elyos has leaked this information.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS13">Of course, I can&apos;t know for definite until we have investigated everything.</Text>
	<Text label="REAL14">I have therefore decided that we need someone to keep a watchful eye on the Orcs.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS15">That person will have to infiltrate the Orcs&apos; base and find out who is behind all this.</Text>
	<Text label="SOL16">Sorry? What? But not...</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS17">Haha! You&apos;re looking a little pale. Please, don&apos;t look so shocked.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS18">It doesn&apos;t matter how much we trust you, we wouldn&apos;t order you to enter a base that is teeming with Orcs.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS19">Well, it wouldn&apos;t have been too much of a problem in my younger days. But you might find it is too much for you.</Text>
	<Text label="REAL20">Stop mocking me and just keep talking.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS21">I only called you because I have come up with a solution. Do you know a witch who goes by the name of Drenon Mines?</Text>
	<Text label="SOL22">Yes, from the catapult mission.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS23">Then let&apos;s not beat about the bush. Go and find the old dear. She will have prepared a potion that will help you to infiltrate the Orc Cave undetected.</Text>
	<Text label="REAL24">The Captain of the Orcs is called Shandu. If you eavesdrop on the Kobold Engineers, we&apos;ll find out his location.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS25">The glass on the tree controls the prison in the harbour. You will meet him there.</Text>
	<Text label="REAL26">I wish you good luck, then.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS27">What?! Yurid, that nutcase?</Text>
	<Text label="REAL28A">Did you really see them?</Text>
	<Text label="SOL28B">Yes, it was definitely them.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS29A">You must summon the Knights and the Red Flame Squad immediately and destroy them!</Text>
	<Text label="REAL29B">...</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS30A">Mikael, you need to make a decision!</Text>
	<Text label="REAL30B">Calm down. Didn&apos;t you foresee this, but there just isn&apos;t any evidence?</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS31">Are you hanging onto your own flesh and blood, even though the situation has deteriorated so badly?!</Text>
	<Text label="REAL32">No, it&apos;s not like that. We mustn&apos;t launch a preemptive strike unless we know what their plans are.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS33">If that&apos;s the way you want it...</Text>
	<Text label="REAL34">The fact that they are provoking the Elyos of their own accord means they are up to something much bigger.</Text>
	<Text label="REAL35">Let&apos;s start by telling the commanding officers at each outpost to increase the number of scouts so they can keep an eye on the Orcs&apos; movements at all times.</Text>
	<Text label="BELUS36">OK, I see.</Text>
	<Text label="REAL37">Oh yeah, I&apos;d forgotten about you. Thank you [%username]. We couldn&apos;t have found it without you.</Text>
	<Text label="REAL38">You can claim the reward for your services from Telia outside the Audience Chamber.</Text>
	<Text label="SOL39">Thank you very much.</Text>
</CutSceneText>
