<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<CutSceneText>
	<Text label="wife0">Darling!</Text>
	<Text label="wife1">I told you to plug the hole in the sandbag!</Text>
	<Text label="wife2">Didn&apos;t you hear me?!</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun3">Darling! Hey, wait a sec! Please listen to what I&apos;ve got to say.</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun4">I didn&apos;t do it because my body wasn&apos;t willing.</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun5_0">Hush now!</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun5_1">...</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun5_1">Deadly attack by the Ratuson Clan!</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun5_2">Oh, a real fire dance!</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun6">Wait here for a sec. I just need to speak with my wife briefly.</Text>
	<Text label="wife7">But darling! Where on earth have you been?</Text>
	<Text label="wife8">I told you to plug the hole in the sandbag, didn&apos;t I?!</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun9">Couldn&apos;t you get one of the slaves to do it? Why are you always getting me to do things like that?</Text>
	<Text label="wife10">Because you&apos;re weak, of course! Aren&apos;t you aware that only the strong ones are served in our family?</Text>
	<Text label="wife10_1">If you were a strong man, I wouldn&apos;t be behaving like this!</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun11">Well I&apos;ll show you that my body isn&apos;t weak. What can I do to get you to acknowledge that my body is strong?</Text>
	<Text label="wife12">Ooh! Then bring me back at least one Crestlich from the Ishalgen Wilderness. Then I&apos;ll acknowledge it.</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun13">Right. I&apos;ll go and catch a Crestlich myself.</Text>
	<Text label="wife13_1">You? Who can&apos;t even use a weapon? Hahaha, I think I might die laughing!</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun13_2">Wait a moment. But seriously now...</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun14">Darling, I&apos;m back. Check this out.</Text>
	<Text label="wife15">Is that a... Crestlich?! You didn&apos;t actually...?</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun16">This is the proof that I put my life on the line to catch a Crestlich. What do you think?</Text>
	<Text label="wife17">I&apos;m impressed!</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun18">Now do you acknowledge that I&apos;m no weakling?</Text>
	<Text label="wife19">Of course! You&apos;re a big strong man.</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun20">Did you hide your strength from me on purpose? Hmm, yes. You could say that. But it&apos;s a disgrace that I had to prove my strength to my own wife.</Text>
	<Text label="wife21">So that&apos;s it. I see... I won&apos;t ignore you any more, or beat you without reason.</Text>
	<Text label="wife22">I love you, darling.</Text>
	<Text label="eikerun23">Oh, I&apos;m really embarrassed. It&apos;s good that you know now. Hahaha...</Text>
</CutSceneText>
